

Kadir Güllüoğlu

Flutter Developer

kadirrgulluoglu@gmail.com

+90 532 175 21 75

★ kadirgulluoglu

in abdulkadirgulluoglu 🕝 kadirgulluoglu

₽ PROFILE

passionate and dedicated Computer Engineer, I bring a wealth of knowledge and experience in mobile application development, with a primary focus on Flutter. Additionally, I have a versatile skill set that extends to PHP Laravel and Swift development, allowing me to create robust and efficient solutions across various platforms.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineer

Harran University 2018 - 2022 | Şanlıurfa, Turkey

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Flutter Developer

AyzaSoft

PHP Laravel

08/2022 - present | Şanlıurfa, Turkey I develop company-specific applications and I am also the team leader

® SKILLS

Flutter	••••
Swift	• • • • •
Algorithm & Data structures	• • • • •
00P	••••
Firebase	• • • • •
Git	••••

P OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

SmartBreath *∂*

(TUBITAK Supported, Flutter)

Mobile Application Integrated with Smart Clock, I use Google maps and Firebase

DALL-E Image generator *⊘*

(Flutter)

I used OpenAI DALL-E image generator api with Flutter

Sync-Music *⊘*

(Flutter)

Spotify app clone and sync music

TravelApp *⊘*

(Flutter)

Travel mobile app

Sentiment Analysis In Chat ∅

(Flutter)

Analyze the emotional state of the other person according to the message sent while messaging

Object Detection @

(Flutter)

Object, Fruit and Coin recognition - Convert Image to Text

RPS with Hand Gestures *⊘*

(Flutter)

Rock Paper Scissors game with hand gestures using image recognition

Personal Portfolio Website @

Kadir Güllüoğlu portfolio website

SPECIAL PROJECT

Dental

0000

(Flutter)

I have had the privilege of spearheading the development of a comprehensive dental automation application. This project aimed to streamline and enhance the management processes within dental practices, offering a seamless solution for both practitioners and patients.

ÇiftçiBilir

(Flutter)

I had the privilege of leading the development of a CiftciBilir mobile application, designed to empower farmers and agricultural enthusiasts with a platform for convenient and efficient shopping tailored to their unique needs.

₽ HAKKIMDA

Tutkulu ve kendini adamış bir Bilgisayar Mühendisi olarak, öncelikli olarak Flutter'a odaklanarak mobil uygulama geliştirme konusunda zengin bilgi ve deneyim sunuyorum. Ek olarak, PHP Laravel ve Swift geliştirmeye kadar uzanan, çeşitli platformlarda sağlam ve etkili çözümler oluşturmamı sağlayan çok yönlü bir beceri setine sahibim.

PROFESYONEL DENEYIM

Flutter Developer

AyzaSoft

08/2022 - present

Flutter ile şirkete özel uygulamalar geliştiriyorum aynı zamanda takım lideriyim.

ဦး EĞITIM

Bilgisayar Mühendisi

Harran Üniversitesi

2018 - 2022 | Şanlıurfa, Türkiye

ஓ AÇIK KAYNAK PROJELER

SmarthBreath ∂

(TUBİTAK Destekli, Flutter)

Akıllı Saat ile bluetooth aracılığıyla entegreli, Google Haritalar ve Firebase ile bağlantılı mobil uygulama

DALL-E Image generator *⊘*

Open Al Resim oluşturucu API kullanılarak yazılan cümleden resim oluşturan mobil uygulama

Sync-Music ∂

(Flutter)

Spotify tasarımına sahip ve aynı zamanda iki ayrı cihazdan eş zamanlı müzik çalma özelliği mevcut

TravelApp ⊘

(Flutter)

Seyahat mobil uygulaması

Sohbette Duygu Analizi 🔗

(Flutter, Python)

Sohbet ederken karşı tarafın duygularını yazdığı mesajın analizine göre gösteren bir doğal dil işleme projesidir.

Obje Tanıma ∂

(Flutter)

Obje, Meyve ve Para Tanıma, Resimdeki yazıları direkt olarak erişmeyi sağlayan mobil uygulama

Taş Kağıt Makas(El Hareketlerine Göre) ∂

(Flutter)

Görüntü işleme kullanılarak kamera karşısında elinizi takip ederek robota karşı interaktif bir şekilde taş kağıt makas oyunu deneyimi sunar.

Kişisel Portföy Web Sitem ⊘

Kendimi tanıttığım kişisel web sitem

ÖZEL PROJELER

Dental

(Flutter)

Diş hekimleri için özel olarak geliştirilmiş randevu, hesap, tedavi, raporlama, stok takip vb. ekranlar bulunan gelişmiş bir mobil uygulama. Tedavi ekranı görsellerle desteklenmiş olup 5000 den fazla tedavi görseli bulunmaktadır. Randevu Ekranı Full Calendar yapıya sahiptir.

Çiftçi Bilir

(Flutter)

Çiftçiler için ikinci el alışveriş yapabileceği bir mobil uygulama